[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Little squirrel.
Are you here to rescue me?
You... if you can get me down,
I'll give you all my food.
Look... you... what do you say?
Mr. Fang, you're awake.
I'm not dead yet?
No, you're not.
I'll figure out a way to get you down.
Falling from such a height,
and I'm still not dead.
Don't they say Heaven envies genius?
Guess I haven't reached that level of genius yet.
This place is surrounded by mountains.
The scenery is beautiful.
Hanging on this tip is quite nice too.
Hanging from this tip,
it's like leaving future archaeologists
a real puzzle to solve.
What other writer ends up hanging to death like this?
Seriously.
It hurts!
Don't move, Mr. Fang!
Stop hitting! It hurts!
Well...
Mr. Fang, wait for me here.
I'll go get help.
Don't come back.
Okay?
No.
Okay.
Is anybody there?!
Is anybody out there?!
Anybody out there?!
Hello? Anybody here?!
Hello?!
Is anybody there?!
Mr... Mr. Fang.
Are you okay?
Holding my pee is making me miserable.
I looked around.
There's no one.
I don't have any other way
to get you down.
I'll just jump down myself.
One more fall won't make a difference.
Then I'll catch you, Mr. Fang.
Don't catch me. Stay back!
It's fine!
I'm afraid I'll crush you.
Alright.
Here I come.
Here goes.
Come on.
Mr. Fang, are you okay?
Oh, my god!
What are you doing, Mr. Fang?
Are you okay?
I'm not!
What's wrong?
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be despised by the entire internet.
I wouldn't have been shocked by that stun baton
all night long!
If it weren't for you,
I would've been driving a Rolls-Royce with my dad,
holding 20 billion
and an iPhone 18 Max Pro Max,
reunited in the next world!
If it weren't for you,
I'd be dead by now!
What does that have to do with me?
I get it now.
If I want to die,
I have to kill you first!
Oh, my god!
Mr. Fang, are you alright?
You must be out of energy by now.
I'm doing fine.
I was afraid you couldn't keep up.
I kept thinking I was chasing you.
Turns out you were walking me.
Are you rested up, Mr. Fang?
Come on. Come on.
Alright.
I'll go back to bashing myself to death.
Mr... Mr. Fang!
Fell for it, didn't you? You fell for it! You fell for it!
Fell for it, didn't you, Dumbass?
That's what you get for following me.
Mr. Fang.
I know you have bipolar disorder.
If hitting me makes your condition
a little bit better,
then go ahead and hit me.
Cut the crap! Nonsense!
Let me tell you something,
I'm not sick!
It was all a lie!
Lied to you, you Dumbass!
Only you would believe it, you know?
Look at you.
How did you even come into this world?
How could your mom give birth to such a Dumbass?
Mr. Fang, don't you dare insult my mom.
I just did. So what?
Your mom's a Dumbass!
You're a Dumbass!
Your whole family are Dumbasses!
Your mom is a Dumbass!
Your dad is a Dumbass too!
You're just a family of Dumbasses!
What about it?
What do you want?
I hate you.
I declare that, from today on,
I'm no longer your fan!
Get lost! Get lost! Get lost!
Fine, I'll get lost!
Get lost!
Even if I leave, you can't insult my mom!
Dumbass!
Because of Mr. Fang Haowen's words,
I make shredded potatoes even better now.
Today, my classmates called me a Dumbass.
I was really angry.
But Mr. Fang's words encouraged me.
Thank you, Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang.
Thank you for your book.
It got me through the hardest days.
Don't jump!
I don't want you to die.
It's not as good as the first one.
Now I'm upset.
Wait, don't be. Let me keep reading.
What if it gets better?
Don't be afraid of failure.
Hope is always there.
Bie Fan.
Are you mad?
Hello.
Hello? Is anyone there?
How did you get in here?
You know me?
I don't care who you are.
This is a wildlife nature reserve.
It's very dangerous.
You need to leave now.
I... I'm lost. I...
Hello, this is Song Qing.
There's someone lost here with me.
What's your name?
I'm already lost, I... I...
just don't ask for my name.
It's too embarrassing.
Please send a car to pick him up.
What? There was a landslide?
You can't get in?
So it'll take a few days.
Alright.
Just make it as quick as possible.
You'll have to stay here for a few days.
Is that okay?
What else can we do?
How did you get lost?
I had a fight with a friend of mine.
You were with a friend?
Bie Fan.
Bie Fan...
I've looked for so long and didn't see him.
He probably made it out.
I hope so.
You're a girl,
living alone in this forest?
I don't live here all the time.
Just about three months a year.
Aren't you scared?
With plants and animals keeping me company,
what is there to be scared of?
O-Or rather, aren't you lonely?
Loneliness is because
you've never learned to be with yourself.
This is called a seven-colored ladybug.
It's a rare insect that
mainly lives in valleys.
Seven-colored ladybugs differ from normal ones
that only have one color.
They, you know,
often come in many, many different colors.
As they grow up,
they have to molt many times.
But every time they molt,
their colors become even more vibrant.
Look.
These little creatures,
they never feel lonely.
Because they just live in the moment.
Always living in harmony with nature.
I've molted many times too,
but my colors only get duller.
Look.
Their backs shine with dazzling colors.
But they, you know,
just crawl along quietly on their own.
Not showy, not impatient.
Every wing
is a color gifted by nature.
So nice.
Look.
Beautiful flower, isn't it?
It's called Viburnum.
Its flowers are as white as snow,
forming a ball of many tiny blossoms.
It's so beautiful.
So many beautiful things in the mountains.
I never noticed them.
I've just never noticed them at all.
Yeah.
Actually, nature has many
very beautiful things.
You just need a pair of eyes
that can discover beauty.
Y-Your eyes are more beautiful than mine.
Let's go.
Oh, Bie Fan.
It has a type of algae on it called
Jolly orange algae.
Don't touch it.
Don't underestimate this little flower.
It's called Corydalis.
It's a traditional Chinese medicine.
It improves circulation and relieves pain.
It usually grows in
mild and moist environments.
You know so much.
Bie Fan.
Come here.
Come on.
Bie Fan.
Where'd you go?
Be careful.
You can find so much profound meaning
in these animals and plants.
I really admire you.
Every creature has its own story.
The most important thing is
to acknowledge their existence
and feel their strength.
Feel their what?
Strength.
It... It fell.
I'll pick it up for you.
No need.
Okay.
Thank you.
Maybe in this forest, I really can
find a sanctuary of my own.
Thank you, Song Qing.
You don't need to thank me.
You should thank nature.
It's taught me so much.
Maybe it can teach you a few things too.
Look at these little lights.
They're like life's little joys.
They flicker occasionally,
but never last.
Sometimes, the brevity of these lights
is exactly what makes them more beautiful.
Maybe I'm just like these lights.
Destined not to stick around for long.
Life is short.
It passes in a flash.
You can't take anything with you.
All that's left behind
are just a few memories.
Even though we don't know each other well,
I still feel you're a bit pessimistic.
Why must you take something with you?
Isn't enjoying the present beauty enough?
You don't know what I've been through.
I may not know what you've been through,
but I do know
imperfection is also a kind of beauty.
Imperfection is also a kind of beauty.
Do you think I'm perfect?
I'm definitely not perfect.
So do you think I'm beautiful?
I think you're pretty great.
I don't believe you.
Believe me now?
I do.
It's getting late. Let's go to sleep.
I'll take the outside, you take the inside.
You take the outside. You take it.
Is... is that okay?
It is. What else?
Song Qing
Song Qing, are you asleep?
May I ask where the bathroom is?
Song Qing! Song Qing!
I'm in the mountains.
Do you remember the guy we talked about?
The one who went viral.
It's him.
I told him a landslide trapped us here.
So I kept him here.
Right now,
I have a video of him harassing me.
I got it all on camera.
Don't you know those, um,
celebrity gossip accounts?
Can you ask them
if this video is worth anything?
He actually kissed me.
It was so gross.
Who knows when he last brushed his teeth.
Call the police?
How am I supposed to make money then, sis?
I'll give you a cut, okay?
Blacklisted?
Believe me now?
Song Qing
No need to see me off.
Stop messing around, you hear me?
I hate you.
Do you have to force me to say
such hurtful things?
I hate you.
Just go.
Who's there?
I'm warning you, it's the middle of the night.
Don't play tricks on me!
I am a martial artist!
In elementary school, I won
1st prize in a youth martial arts contest!
I've written two martial arts manuals!
Seven or eight men can't even touch me!
So what if you're a wild beast?
Wolves, bears,
even a tiger...
I'll kill you in three punches!
Try me if you don't believe it!
You think I...
Come at me if you dare!
One-on-one!
Freeze!
Vile beast, cease your attack!
Master, come quickly!
Look.
Benefactor, apologies for the scare.
I'm dreaming, right? I'm... I'm dreaming.